Every role in the company is deserved.  There is
nothing that is inherited.  Even if
you've been in a role for 4 years, if there's
someone who's a better fit than
you, it's right that that person gets
that opportunity, because otherwise you're doing
everyone a disservice.
How has your role in this changed since I
last
interviewed you?  In fact,
I decided to step down for a couple
of reasons.  I realized that that role wasn't a
good fit for
my skills.  I mean, I made it and I love it, I
worked on it for a long time, I
developed an expertise, but I'm not
very good at managing so many fronts
at the same time.  I function best
when I can focus on one
project at a time, and when
you're managing so much, you're exposed to a
lot of complexity, things
coming at you from all over the place, it's hard
to focus on getting
one project done and then moving on
to the next.  Another reason
why I decided to take this step down is
the fact that the person who replaced me
in that role is much better than
me.  No one's role is sacred, and
any role must be earned.